briskom.com 2014-10-22

# Briskom : Ultimate Database of Classified

Maintaining the absolute privacy pertaining to all our users is the key factor for our concern. From all users of Briskom, it is primarily expected that they are well aware of the fact that using any of our specific online feature for free classified may lead to publication. Moreover, they should well-accept that they are not only responsible themselves for the authenticity of their ad posting but are also the sole bearers for the consequences of sharing their personal information on our streams online. Furthermore, users are entitled to engage with us, provided they accept and agree upon our policy terms applicable on each of our stream, be it available on existing or new.

The information provided to us voluntarily from your end is publicly available online. However, being the beholders of your personal details, we solely take the responsibility of keeping all information collected by you, be it via email or other direct mediums of contact, completely safe and strictly confidential while accessing it and would never be shared with any external organization. We hereby have the right to sell or rent your classified ads for free online, although your personal information will not be leaked anywhere without your explicit consent. Moreover, reasonable steps are initiated by our team to protect all such information from any kind of misuse, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Be rest assured for the same as we at Briskom firmly believe in encouraging safe trading with market communications while introducing great promotional offers to you. However, You can review your free online classified ad posting and even modify or erase your personal information by logging onto your account status page. 

On the contrary, Briskom does reserve the right to retain and utilize the personal information of fraudulent users dealing with unethical transactions, who are subject to legal investigation or judicial proceedings. Also, if a particular content posted by any user on our stream violates some third party's rights, in that case we might use his/her personal information as well, to respond to such claims, to resolve internal disputes or in troubleshooting problems which are liable to our policy enforcement. 

Lastly but most importantly, being an existing Briskom user, you are liable to use the personal information of other users gathered by us provided you are willing to follow up with them for dealing with their specific postings, regardless of engaging in any kind of spam/phishing or collecting their information without their permission. 

If you have any further query regarding our privacy policy, please free to contact us at webmaster@briskom.com . Our team would get in touch with you at the earliest.

We ensure that our entire privacy policy would be highly effective and reliable as well !
